<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>RealitExper</title>
    <description>Awesome website.This website was designed in order to make my publications whether writen by me or my friend usefull for my other friends.
</description>
    <link>http://RealitExper.com/Reality/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://RealitExper.com/Reality/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 23:59:30 +0100</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 23:59:30 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.6</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Practise happiness!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Money can not buy happiness. We are all familiar with this saying. But do we really believe in this especially nowadays in time where everyone may dream of having a palace or a beatifull house, a beautifull housewive or husband (in short a beautifull of everything!!) and yet still missing something. haha :p&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The most of us would still be left feeling unfulfilled even if we have all of these, as if something is srill missing from our lives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even if you do not feel happy, or do not feel as if you can simply decide to be happy, you can practice happiness. Make conscious decisions every day to choose to be as happy as you can be. &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Pick positive things to say about yourself&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;choose positive thoughts&lt;/code&gt;, and &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;eliminate old patterns of negative, depressing thoughts&lt;/code&gt;. The more you do this, and the more effort you put into it each day, &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;the easier it can be to actually become happy. Yes, you can practice being happy to become happy!&lt;/code&gt; What a wonderful concept.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[Operationmeditation.com]&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 14:09:16 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://RealitExper.com/Reality/Practise_happiness.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://RealitExper.com/Reality/Practise_happiness.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>....</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Learn to overcome fear of failure</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Honestly, most of us haven’t yet decided what we want to achieve in life. Your inner voice constantly reminds you of all the negative things that instill unknown fears within you. You are not really sure about your decision and whether you should really work hard for a change. The only thing you need to keep in mind is that it is never too late to change your attitude or behavior. All you need to do is boost your motivation and make your goals more appealing.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://RealitExper.com/Reality/Learn-to-overcome-fear-of-failure.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://RealitExper.com/Reality/Learn-to-overcome-fear-of-failure.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Adventure in time blocking</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;People have ideas, but don’t remember them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What you need is a Spark File.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The basic idea is this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;codehilite&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;Whenever you have a hunch or idea, put them together in remind. And don&#39;t judge them, don&#39;t think about them, just put them in there. And wait for the right time to grab them. Maybe one day that idea can become true. Who knows! 


Put a recurring calendar event - every 2-3 months (take your pick) seems like a good pace.
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Return to your spark file every time that event comes up. Re-read the whole thing, from start to finish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Who knows - maybe you’ll start to see a pattern of ideas around a topic. Or you’ll see things that can fit together in a blog post.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://RealitExper.com/Reality/Adventure-in-time-blocking.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://RealitExper.com/Reality/Adventure-in-time-blocking.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
